(Self-sufficiency)
- It's good to see you again. - It's good to see you.
Let's meet today's Rainbow Live guest.
On stage, he shows an impressive performance.
Off stage, fans love him for his unique sensibility.
- It's DAWN! - DAWN.
(Let us introduce DAWN.)
DAWN.
(Smiling)
(He became known for his dreamy aesthetic.)
("DAWN Builds His Own Musical World Through Songwriting and Producing")
("All-Round Musician Who Has Written and Produced Since His Solo Debut")
(He's a well-rounded artist who writes and produces his own music.)
(A multi-talented musician, DAWN)
(It's good to see you.)
- Oh, gosh. - Oh, my.
You little cutie.
- Hi, cutie. - How adorable.
- Hi, puppy. - How cute.
- No one has come with their dog. - Right.
What's its name?
Her name is Haetnim.
- Haetnim. - She's a female dog.
- She doesn't look nervous. - She's so well-behaved.
- Is she always like that? - You little cutie.
He loves having a dog around.
- There you go again. - She's beautiful.
- Sit. - Sit.
- Sit. - Sit, Haetnim.
There you go. You're amazing.
Oh, yes.
She seems to know her right side looks better on camera.
- Always showing her right side. - Always showing her right side.
- Please say hello to the viewers. - Sure.
Hello, I'm DAWN.
I do music.
Awesome.
DAWN is known for his aesthetics...
- on social media. - Right.
As far as I know, he loves...
mixing unexpected pieces and has a thing for vintage items.
He's so cool.
- He's cool. - He's Hyun Moo's...
- style icon. - Yes.
- His fashion. - And style.
- I have my own YouTube channel. - Okay.
So many people mention Hyun Moo in the comments.
- What? Why? - Why?
"Hyun Moo would love this."
"You should go on I Live Alone." There are so many comments.
- So many people say that. - Really? Is your style aesthetic?
(His heart is beating.)
Please give me your number later.
That's so sudden.
That definitely got my attention.
- He has great taste. - I need to learn from him.
Let's take a look at his daily life.
(Let's step into his daily life.)
- How cute. - She's so well-behaved.
- She's so calm. - She's so gentle.
- You're adorable. - You can rest.
(Slowly at DAWN's Own Pace)
(A bright room with sunlight pouring in)
You don't have blackout curtains?
I like letting the sunlight wake me up naturally.
I don't have curtains in my house.
(Wriggling)
(He wakes up naturally with the sunlight.)
Hello, I'm Singer DAWN,
and this is my fourth year living on my own.
(I need to wake up quickly.)
(Springing)
- It's Haetnim we saw earlier. - It's Haetnim.
How adorable.
(Haetnim also woke up.)
(Rolling)
(He drags himself out of bed...)
(and makes it first.)
(Pulling up)
(He raises the blind and opens the window to let some fresh air in.)
You must air out the room.
(Come here.)
She's so cute.
Her name is Haetnim.
Was it 2019 or 2020?
At first, someone I know...
wanted to adopt a dog,
preferably from a shelter.
- So we went together. - Oh, my.
- My gosh. - I fell in love with Haetnim...
- and ended up coming home with her. - She looks happier now.
- She looks more handsome. - Yes. She looks a lot better now.
She's my soulmate.
- You can tell her anything. - Yes.
(He walks out of the room with his soulmate.)
Well...
(Clean)
- It doesn't look like a house. - It's unique.
- It's like an exhibit hall. - Yes, it's like an exhibit hall.
(He walks across the exhibit hall...)
(and opens the curtains.)
- The windows are arched. - Arched windows?
That's my dream window.
(Shin Young's dream arched windows come into view.)
(Relaxed)
It was the second floor.
It looks like it takes 30 seconds to come down the stairs.
(He opens the curtains on the 1st floor as well.)
- It's really interesting. - It's a nice place.
It looks pretty.
(Welcome to DAWN's tranquil house.)
Oh, my.
This is a two-story house.
It's a house, not an apartment. That's my dream.
I like preserving original features...
instead of getting rid of them.
I prefer working with what's already there.
The first floor had wainscoting...
on only one wall.
So I wanted to mix in some Eastern-inspired pieces.
That's why I filled the space with a lot of custom-made items.
(A custom-made sofa set created to complement the space)
- It's pretty. - What is that?
Those were the kinds of things you'd see in a CEO's home...
- back then. - I know. Back in the day.
- The intertwined vines. - In the past... Yes.
Do you know how much the table cost?
- Okay. - Can you guess?
- Shall we? - It must be quite expensive.
Even a single branch...
in my vivarium can cost around 100 to 200 dollars.
How much is the table then?
Isn't it over 10,000 dollars?
It must be expensive.
- It'd be around 15,000 dollars. - I think it's 20,000 dollars.
- You think it's 20,000 dollars? - Yes, it's 20,000 dollars.
It's 50 dollars.
- What, 50 dollars? - Hold on.
Oh, boy. We were completely wrong.
I spent ages searching for a table like that...
- on secondhand apps. - You did?
Then I found someone who was getting rid of one.
- Yes. - I even brought it home myself...
to save on delivery costs.
The original price must've been pretty high, though.
- It must've been expensive. - It was expensive.
It must've cost a lot. The table ended up with the right person.
- Right. - It looks amazing.
- It looks so cool. - It's a really good one.
Looking around, you'll notice objects...
that reflect Korean culture.
It's pretty.
It's very unique.
(DAWN has a unique and sophisticated taste.)
What's this?
(Immersed)
It looks like he stole cultural treasures...
- from all over the world. - I know.
(Walking past the living room, you're greeted by a dining room...)
(brimming with character.)
The previous owner left that light fixture behind.
What?
- That's expensive. - Those are expensive in stores.
- That one? - Yes.
- No. That's from IKEA. - What?
IKEA?
(No way!)
(I definitely bought out IKEA.)
You went there. Why didn't you see that?
Why couldn't you find an item like that?
I'll make you one just by crumpling up some tissue paper.
Yes. You're an artist too.
(I'll make one for you.)
(Past the IKEA lamp is a display cabinet.)
My house is like a museum.
(Heading upstairs from the museum-like 1st floor)
(The interior takes a 180° turn.)
It looks like a studio.
- There's a sculptor I know. - Oh, my.
That's the statue...
I received as a gift.
On the second floor, I just placed the things I love...
without overthinking it.
It brings back my dream of living in a house.
(One wall features a painting he created himself.)
- Do you paint too? - Yes.
- I painted it. - You painted it?
- Yes. - I thought it was done...
by a professional artist.
Me too.
(Shy)
(Sliding)
(He calmly opens the windows and front door.)
(It takes forever.)
(Taking his time, he brushes his teeth, washes his face,)
(and slathers on some lotion.)
(Heave-ho)
(Grabbing)
(He takes out the ingredients without a second thought.)
- What is he going to eat? - I'm so curious.
(Curious)
Cheese.
(He took out cheese in the morning.)
(Pressing)
(Pressing again)
It's not playing at half speed, is it?
Was the knife dull?
My nickname was Sloth.
- Is that salami? - My goodness.
(Taking his time, he slices the salami.)
(Peaceful)
I don't usually eat breakfast.
I just drink coffee or tea.
I put out some biscuits,
- salami, cheese, and honey... - My goodness.
to make an easy finger food platter.
That's what I ate.
(For breakfast, he has a simple finger food platter.)
They go well with wine. Why is he eating them...
- in the morning? - I know.
- Those are for wine. - Wine.
I love them.
(He grabs a jar of honey.)
(He takes out a big spoonful.)
(The food is ready.)
(He opens the fridge again.)
- What? Are those soft drinks? - Soft drinks?
(Why did he take out soft drinks?)
- Black raspberry? - I see.
It's good for stamina.
(He pours it over black raspberry juice.)
(He carefully pours the mixture into the glass.)
(Satisfied)
(He walks past the dining table.)
(Plopping down)
- My goodness. - Haetnim is next to him.
(Right outside the front door)
It has always been a dream of mine to own a yard even if it's small.
It's my own yard.
(The small-sized yard has been DAWN's dream.)
(Chirping)
Are birds chirping?
- Are those actual sounds? - Yes.
I think I turned on the background noise.
Bird chirping sounds?
(Come on...)
(Playing the background noise)
He is similar to me.
- You always do the same. - Bird chirping sounds.
- I always play them. - Same here.
If you have a lot of grass in the yard,
insects and mosquitoes enter the house.
When insects enter the house...
I don't catch any insects other than mosquitoes.
- Same here! - Are you serious?
- Really? - Yes!
- Really? - I can't believe it.
(He relaxes as he listens to the bird chirping sounds.)
(Shall I eat now?)
(Salty olives and cool black raspberry ade)
I wanted a wine-like drink.
- I see. - I see.
- My goodness. - It's the Mediterranean.
It feels like you're abroad.
(The salami canapes suit the yard.)
You put the food on the railing.
- Yes. - I see.
(He puts cheese on the cracker.)
(Then he puts honey...)
(and salami on the top.)
(He puts the entire thing in his mouth.)
(Patting)
(Chewing)
His eyes make me feel like he has no will to live.
I know. It's like "The Last Leaf."
I bet that drink goes well with the food.
It's nice that he is so relaxed.
(He tries a sip of black raspberry ade.)
(Dazed)
She has the same facial expression.
- She resembles him. - How cute!
She is so cute.
(Wagging her tail)
- She is so obedient. - She is like a human.
Haetnim is hungry. That's right.
- Oh, my. - She wants DAWN to share.
"Give me my food."
Haetnim has gained a lot of weight.
- She doesn't look that way. - I feed her only at set times.
Managing your dog's weight is important.
- I need to manage her weight. - That's right.
(He looks at the yard.)
(Slouching)
I always sit there.
It's my favorite spot.
Apparently, I have adrenal fatigue.
I need a lot of sunlight.
The big tree that's right in front of the spot is a magnolia tree.
In spring, magnolias blossom.
In winter, snow falls...
and piles up...
- on the branches. - Oh, my.
He set up a tent in the yard.
It's so nice. Haetnim always rests there too.
(Haetnim also likes the yard.)
I'm obsessed with the scenery.
You don't take care of those weeds, right?
No, I don't. They die in winter.
That's it!
(That's it!)
- I also... - Stop saying you're the same.
- Stop inserting yourself. - Seriously.
- What is it this time? - I think...
people who live in houses are divided into two types.
You're nothing like him.
They either manage the house meticulously or leave it be.
- I'm totally the latter. - Only those two types...
- live in a house. - Really?
You leave it be as well, but it has different vibes.
- Totally different vibes. - Your house is nothing like his.
Your house is a bit different.
(I enjoyed the food.)
Shall we go inside?
(Heave-ho)
I'm so jealous that he lives in a house.
(After breakfast, he gets changed in a relaxed way.)
Okay.
(Grabbing)
(He grabs the notebook and walks over to the living room.)
Okay. Let's go.
- A timer? Does that mean... - A timer?
(Okay. Let's go.)
- Oh, my. - My goodness.
You've changed a lot.
What's this?
This workout lets me finish everything in 30 minutes.
It's the DAWN Challenge Workout.
I start a stopwatch...
and do a set per minute.
After doing ten sets,
I rest for ten minutes.
A 10-minute rest after 1 set?
I rest for 10 minutes. When I have 10 minutes rest,
I do it again. So...
I exercise for 20 minutes.
It must be hard.
(Shoulder tap push-ups)
- What? - I can't believe it.
- He must've done this many times. - He is so flexible.
(He moves front and back once.)
(After the squats, 1 set is done.)
So that's one set.
It's really hard to do one set.
- It looks very hard. - Of course.
(He catches his breath for a second.)
(He starts the 2nd set right away.)
(He does push-ups with shoulder and ankle taps.)
(Then he continues with squats.)
(After one set, he catches his breath again.)
(Then he starts the 3rd set right away.)
(Then comes the 4th set.)
(Then comes the 5th set.)
- Do you do ten sets? - Yes.
That's intense.
It's exhausting.
It isn't easy to do that for 30 minutes.
(He easily clears 10 sets.)
How intense.
All done.
(Grabbing)
(He sets up the mat as he catches his breath.)
(What is he doing?)
- Are you singing? - That came out of nowhere.
(Why did he suddenly begin singing?)
I do that...
because I dance and sing on the stage.
You want to improve your lung capacity.
(My break is coming to an end.)
(After checking the time)
What next?
(He gets ready for the next exercise.)
Will he do jumps?
Oh, my.
(Sliding push-ups)
You set up the mat for that.
Kim Moo Yul's bodyweight workout with push-ups...
was so cool.
- That's right. - I see.
(Moo Yul's push-ups made DAWN want to try them.)
I wanted to try them, so I incorporated them into my workout.
(He slides using the foot mat as support.)
It has been two months since I began the challenge.
Really? How can you do it so well in two months?
- Push-ups are hard enough. - After ten sets...
(He does 10 sets this time as well.)
He has a strong core.
He has a great core.
(Grunting)
(It's finally over.)
(Panting)
(Breathing out)
Okay.
Let's wash up now.
It's so hot.
(He goes to wash off his sweat.)
(DAWN is done with his shower.)
I feel so refreshed.
Okay.
Haetnim.
- My goodness. - There she comes.
(She comes when her dad calls her.)
Do you want to go for a walk?
A walk?
(Let's go right away.)
A walk? Do you want to go for a walk?
My goodness.
- A walk? - She loves going for a walk.
(You're so cute.)
She is happy.
(Haetnim doesn't mind having her face scrunched up.)
Let's go.
(Shall we get ready for a walk?)
(She puts her head into the harness.)
- Because she likes going out. - She's smart.
She's very smart.
(He heads outside with Haetnim into the warm sunshine.)
(Slow)
(Haetnim strolls along at a relaxed pace.)
Hello.
(He greets his neighbor and begins his walk.)
Looking at him like this, you can really see his chest muscles.
I haven't heard that word for a while.
You're a former news anchor. You know that's slang for chest muscles.
(He's striding while showing off his pecs.)
Haetnim always does her business outside.
So we need to go outside 3 to 4 times a day.
We have several walking routes that we often take.
There are about four for them.
Does she not poop in the yard?
She thinks it's part of her house.
(I like being outside.)
You're so good at doing your business.
Good job.
(Satisfied)
(After they finished a refreshing walk)
It's hot.
(DAWN and Haetnim came home.)
(He goes straight to the kitchen.)
- Food for Haetnim? - Food for Haetnim?
Food is ready. Come here.
Is that raw meat?
It's raw meat. I feed her raw food.
It must be delicious.
(Gobbling)
(After feeding Haetnim, he goes to the dressing room.)
(Rummaging)
(He got changed and came out.)
(He puts on long socks.)
He's going somewhere.
(He takes out his long boots and gets ready to go out.)
- Long boots. It's summer. - Long boots?
Right. But I like boots.
Is he going to ride a motorcycle?
Haetnim, see you later.
Please behave. Don't cause trouble.
(See you later.)
Look at his chest muscles.
- What? - All I can see are his pecs.
DAWN's pecs.
That's all I can see.
There are shutters.
- What? - Don't try to find a connection.
There are shutters in my house too.
(There are shutters in my house too.)
- But you don't have chest muscles. - I don't.
- If you don't, you're out. - Chest muscles.
- You need pecs. - Your chest is just fat.
He has muscles. You don't.
Exactly.
He's pure fat.
(Getting closer)
- That's an old car. - Yes, I drive an old car.
- Is that a Volvo? - Yes, it's a Volvo.
He's got great style.
(It's parked in a small garage.)
It's an old car.
- It was manufactured in 1998. - In 1998?
- In 1998? - That's what I'm talking about.
- There's a cassette tape player. - A cassette tape player.
You can't put a CD in there.
I always wanted an old car.
It cost 5,000 dollars. I named it Volduk.
It has a name too. Because it's my first car.
Nothing on this car is in good shape.
That's cool too.
If something breaks or falls off, I just tape it back on.
I fix whatever I can myself and keep driving it.
Everything falls off.
Still, I like that car.
Right.
I paid 4,300 dollars for a car.
- I paid 4,200 dollars. - No one will drive it anyway.
I got it for similar reasons.
There are so many camping cars,
but I just wanted to get what I needed at a low price.
- That's all I wanted. - Right.
- I'm not really into cars. - Me neither.
"Me neither?"
- Stop saying, "I'm like that too." - That's enough.
I'm going to get you for that.
- "Me too. I'm like that too." - Don't try to make a connection.
- You two are so different. - It's no joke, sir.
Be quiet.
(It starts with a key.)
(Vroom)
That's the beauty of an old car.
You start it by turning the key.
- Yes. It's not a smart key. - I haven't seen it for a long time.
It's rare these days.
(Setting off with Volduk)
(Only silence)
(Remains)
(Only a sense of loneliness)
(Lingers in the air)
The song is called "After the Play."
(Driving his old car and humming along to an old song,)
(he arrives somewhere.)
- Where is he? - Where is he?
Where is he?
I'm excited.
It's driving me crazy.
It's going to be so pretty.
(Taking each step with anticipation)
(He enters somewhere with a bright smile.)
Where did he go?
- Hello, sir. - Hello.
(Frames are lined up all along both sides.)
Is that a home decor store?
It's a framing shop...
in Eulji-ro.
I left my precious treasure there,
so I went to pick it up today.
- Something to have it framed? - Yes, I left it there.
I've been waiting...
- Really? - for this piece.
Did the photo turn out nice?
- Do you want to take a look? - Yes.
- Did he paint something again? - That's what I'm thinking.
That could be the case.
- A piece of work. - Yes.
(Opening)
- It's so pretty. - Right?
- I love it. - He looks very satisfied.
He has a bright expression on his face.
(A precious treasure he's been waiting for a long time)
- Oh, my. - It's a kite.
It's an old-fashioned kite.
(A shield-shaped kite)
This guy's sense of aesthetics!
Hyun Moo will be looking for a kite.
I'm going to get a kite.
He's looking for a kite on a secondhand app.
This is awesome.
(He loves it.)
I got the kite for my birthday.
It was made by...
- Oh, my. - Bae Mu Sam, the kite artisan.
- A kite artisan? - I love the kite.
It was made by an artisan?
It seems you like things made by artisans.
Yes, I love them.
- You search for them. - Yes.
My house is filled with many pieces made by artisans.
Is that so?
- The fan too. - Yes.
That one too.
Some of them were gifts from artisans,
and some of them are things I bought myself.
I naturally collected objects like that.
- Made by a master umbrella artisan. - A master umbrella artisan.
I love furniture and objects. I was looking for something,
and I found a perfect piece.
It turned out to be...
a piece of Korea's intangible cultural heritage.
It has a long history.
"Moo-hyung heritage?"
- "Moo-hyung," meaning "intangible." - "Moo-hyung."
Hey.
(Moo-hyung?)
- Gosh. - I'm sick of it.
Someone will say "moomoo-hyung."
"Moo-hyung?" Okay.
(Eyes sparkling)
That doesn't sound bad.
Since then, I've been visiting...
intangible cultural heritage artisans.
Those artisans have spent many years...
to perfect a single craft.
I gain so much from hearing their stories.
That's so cool.
I found a news article...
saying that Korea's intangible cultural heritage...
could disappear.
So I wanted to find a way...
to help them.
So I started meeting these artisans...
and introducing them to people.
When they thank me,
it feels strange...
but also very rewarding.
This guy is so...
(Peeking)
It looks amazing.
(A treasure I want to look at again and again)
What does the Chinese character mean?
- "Hong-hong?" - What?
- What's that? - "Hong-hong?"
That's definitely not "hong-hong." It's a Chinese character.
- What are you talking about? - "Hong-hong?"
- What does it say? - "Hong-heung."
"Hom-hom" Like "Come Back Home?"
No.
Come back home
(He can't let go of the memory of that day yet.)
- Come back home - He got zero votes.
I haven't been able to sleep since then.
(Kian84, I haven't been able to sleep since then.)
(Juno84 has been losing sleep since that day.)
- My gosh. - I don't want to go home.
What does the Chinese character mean?
- It means joy. - Joy?
- Joy. - It means joy.
(The joy of learning)
- Okay. Thank you. - You're welcome.
- I'll come again. - Thank you.
(After carefully wrapping it up, he held the shield-shaped kite.)
Okay.
(Happy)
It's so pretty.
It's crazy.
You look so happy.
I was overjoyed.
- He looks excited. - It's something he likes.
I think I would have a lot to talk about with him.
(With his treasure finally in his hands, his steps feel lighter.)
(As always, he hums an old song.)
Is that Gangnam?
He's driving across Dongho Bridge.
(Clanking)
- He pulled up the handbrake. - I haven't seen it for a while.
- I haven't seen it for a while. - It's a handbrake.
(It's good to see it again.)
(He gets out in a quiet residential area.)
He's not going home.
(Sniffing)
(Glancing)
(He puts on a hat.)
Is he stealing something?
- That's a saw. A coping saw. - That's a saw. A coping saw.
- Are you going to steal a bicycle? - A bicycle?
You can't cut the locks people use these days...
- with that saw. - Can't you cut them?
- The locks are strong these days. - Um Bok Dong.
- He is like Um Bok Dong. - Um Bok Dong.
He is like Um Bok Dong.
(DAWN Bok Dong!)
(Walking over)
(He approaches a building.)
(Looking around)
Look at that. It looks like...
- He looked around before entering. - I know.
(He goes straight after looking around.)
This is strange.
(Plopping down)
(Glancing over)
- That's... What? - Oh, my!
- What's going on? - Why are you sawing someone's tree?
(He goes straight after looking around.)
This is strange.
(Plopping down)
(Glancing over)
- That's... What? - Oh, my!
- What's going on? - Why are you sawing someone's tree?
(DAWN,)
(I don't do that.)
He is committing a crime.
I'm not sure if that kite was a gift.
Time out. Are you sure the table was 50 dollars?
Maybe he cut the string with scissors...
when the kite master was flying his kite.
- He is a fence! - I know.
- That's how he gets his items. - I waited for him to fly his kite.
- Seriously. - Do you own a pawn shop?
(Do you own a pawn shop?)
(He saws the tree without hesitation.)
(Glancing over)
It's the office of an acquaintance of mine.
- I see. - I needed...
some bamboo,
so I went there to steal some.
- I see. - He was getting too many bamboos.
He wanted to get rid of them,
so he told me that I could cut them as much as I wanted.
It benefits both of us,
I think.
Then why are you so wary?
There were employees.
- So... - I became a bit wary.
- What if a security comes... - Of course.
and says, "What are you doing?"
- The employees might not know. - That's right.
There were many employees in the building.
- So... - By any chance,
- may I cut some bamboo as well? - What?
- May I cut some bamboo as well? - I think he'll say yes.
Why do you need bamboo?
I'll think about the use afterward.
Think about it beforehand! Please!
- I'll use it sometime. - I can't believe him.
(He wants to call dibs on the cool-looking things.)
I'll use it sometime. Maybe I'll use it as a body pillow.
(Bamboo, I want you.)
(Sawing)
(He cuts down a dead tree.)
That's a dead tree.
- I picked a dead tree. - You cut down a dead tree.
You have conscience, despite everything.
(Joking)
(Absorbed)
- How will he use it? - Bamboo rice?
You could split it and use it to skewer meat.
That's right.
My goodness.
My goodness. That's it.
(He succeeds in separating the tree.)
Okay.
(He succeeds in cutting down a tall bamboo.)
- It won't go into the car. - It was too tall for the car.
- You have to cut it. - You have to cut it.
- You have to cut it. - I did that.
(He begins to cut it.)
(His experienced hands cut the bamboo cleanly.)
- You cut it well. - Yes.
I cut it into smaller pieces.
(He cleans up after himself.)
You cleaned up after yourself.
(The bamboo hunter leaves.)
Thankfully, no one asked me what I was doing.
That's right.
(He returns with his harvest.)
(Opening)
- It's falling apart. - My goodness.
My goodness. Something fell off.
(Hitting)
(He fixes the car easily with two touches.)
That car is difficult to manage,
but I like it.
I love that you're easygoing.
- That's right. - Those things don't bother me.
(He tends to be calm and easygoing.)
(Let's hurry up and go.)
(With bamboo in his car)
- How will he use it? - Bamboo... How strange.
(He arrives home.)
(Wagging her tail)
(He moves his precious frame...)
(and the bamboo into the house.)
Shall I hang it up?
(Lifting)
This is insane.
You must be excited since you got the frame after a long wait.
(Unboxing the frame excitedly)
- Where will he hang it? - Finally.
He must be torn.
(Looking around)
(Where should I hang it?)
Where would you hang it?
I wouldn't hang it anywhere.
I'd leave it on the floor.
(In that case, I'll put it...)
(This is a good spot.)
Will he leave it on the floor?
(He puts it on the floor.)
That was sudden.
(We clicked.)
He is very satisfied.
- It's pretty. - Okay.
It's nice.
All the aspects of the house go well together.
(DAWN's steps are light from excitement.)
(Picking up)
What? I bet he made something.
- What's that? - What? What's that?
- Wire fence? - Wire?
(DAWN brings something out.)
Isn't it a bamboo frame?
- That's why he brought bamboo. - A bamboo frame?
(Shaking)
(He sits on the sofa with the mystery item.)
(Let's take a look.)
It's rattan.
- Rattan? - I see.
It's often used for craft.
I'll use it to make a light.
Will you make it?
I like lights that spread out gently.
I didn't have the money to buy expensive lights,
so I decided to make them.
I've been making them ever since.
How cool.
- Did you make that hanging light? - Yes.
That was my first work.
My very first work.
You have a talent.
I use rattan to make a frame.
(After making the frame, he secures it with a glue gun.)
- Do you use a glue gun? - It can't be easy.
He has a glue gun.
(After making the frame, he secures it with a glue gun.)
(Focused)
(The glue secures the frame as it hardens.)
(He adds one rattan stick at a time...)
(until the frame is done.)
He is absorbed in his work.
You make your own designs...
- instead of copying them, right? - Of course.
- That's right. I go with the flow. - That's the best method.
(He puts one piece...)
(after another...)
(with concentration.)
He makes it like a master.
- Like an intangible cultural asset. - Seriously.
(He is cool.)
(The light frame takes shape.)
(He cuts the pieces that are sticking out.)
Okay.
(The light frame is ready.)
(Mixing)
- I use wood glue. - Wood glue.
I dilute it with water for my use.
You need to dilute it with water for it to dry quickly.
That's right.
(Tearing)
Afterward, I stick...
Korean paper on the frame.
When there are multiple layers of paper,
the light spreads out as if it's a diffuser...
and slowly glows up the room.
I developed it myself.
You've done a lot of observing.
- I've done a lot of research. - Right.
That's really hard to do.
(His past efforts can be seen through his hands.)
(He places each piece carefully.)
(Meanwhile, it became dark outside.)
(He's focused on it without realizing time is flying by.)
This makes me become very focused.
It fills me with all kinds of thoughts.
Rattan actually breaks easily...
before becoming wet with water.
It becomes flexible when it gets wet.
Even when seeing things like that,
it makes me think that a person can break...
if they become too strong.
He even thinks philosophically.
- Becoming flexible... - Right.
would prevent me from breaking...
and living a harder life.
The glue from the glue gun...
is really hot when I touch it from time to time.
When it hardens to a certain point,
I can touch it and change its form.
"When people become hot with emotion,"
"they must not be touched."
Right.
- "When the two cool down..." - I like that.
"and soothe each other,"
"that is when they can form a shape together."
I get these kinds of thoughts.
While fiddling with my hands, I get lost in thought.
I usually sit there for around 6 to 7 hours.
(While quietly getting lost in thought as he uses his hands,)
(he uses this time to solely focus on himself.)
(He finishes up by drying the glue on the Korean paper.)
(The end of the work can be seen.)
(Sleeping)
Whenever I make something,
I give it to the people around me as a gift.
Are you planning to give us gifts as well?
I give it as a gift if someone moves into a new place.
- I'm moving soon. - I'll move.
Right. You can start looking for a new place.
I called dibs.
(DAWN checks the bamboo he chopped in the afternoon.)
(This one should do.)
- I'm really curious about... - What is that for?
- the bamboo he brought. - Right.
I don't have a clue what it's for.
(He picks two stalks of bamboo that are of different thickness.)
(Sawing)
(He saws off part of it.)
(Realizing)
What is it?
(DAWN makes a hole on the thick bamboo stalk.)
- Gosh! - Here comes a masterpiece.
(He makes the hole bigger with scissors.)
(The thinner bamboo stalk is placed into the hole.)
It's just like how nails aren't used...
- when making traditional houses. - Right.
Right.
(He works on the wires next.)
- He works like a professional. - Gosh.
- He can do it all. - It's a light.
(He puts together the bulb that will be used for the light.)
As ready-made bulbs won't fit,
- I make each part separately. - According to the size.
(Pulling out)
(The wire is placed through the connected bamboo stalks.)
(Getting up)
(The bulb that is connected is put into the frame.)
(I'm done now.)
Gosh, it looks nice.
(Lighting up)
(The light turns on after a long time spent.)
(Impressed)
It looks really nice as the bamboo stalk is tall.
(The light has finally come to life.)
- It looks nice. - It looks nice.
Intangible Heritage 61.
That's my dream.
- He made that many of them? - Hold on. Intangible Heritage 61?
So that's the 61st piece?
I just went with 61 since my birthday is June 1.
(I see!)
I came up with a name for the first light that I made...
on the first floor.
It looked like a pupa.
That was why I named it the pupa light.
I really wanted to make another light after that.
So I thought that I should make a light...
expressing the butterfly coming out of the cocoon.
- A butterfly... - There's a story to it.
- coming out of the cocoon. - Gosh.
So it's called the metamorphosis light.
- It makes sense. - There's a story to it.
(The metamorphosis light creator is satisfied with the result.)
I feel so proud.
I'm never going to do this again.
(A twist)
Even after declaring not to do it again,
- You end up doing it again. - I end up doing it again.
- It looks nice, though. - Right.
(Gosh, that was exhausting.)
I should eat now.
I'm hungry.
I should eat.
(He heads to the kitchen while feeling exhausted.)
(It's his first meal after having breakfast.)
- It's his first meal. - Right.
- He really doesn't eat. - Right.
(Dinner is scorched rice?)
- Gosh! - What?
- Gosh. - What?
Sungnyung?
(He adds a generous amount of scorched rice to the pot.)
I love scorched rice.
(He opens the fridge.)
(He heads back after taking something out.)
(Eggs)
- Eggs? Protein? - Protein?
(Whisking)
(He skilfully removes the chalaza as well.)
(This should be enough.)
He's steaming that. Gosh.
(He's ready to make steamed eggs!)
(He gets rid of the tuna oil with a strainer.)
The oil is removed as it's bad for the body.
(After heating up the instant rice,)
(the strained tuna gets added.)
- Rice balls? - He must be mixing it up.
- Tuna mayo? - Gosh, pollack roe!
- He knows how to eat! - Pollack roe mayo!
(The tuna pollack roe mayo is ready.)
(I can't resist it!)
Right. That's how you eat at home.
(Satisfied)
(He gets a piece of gamtae next.)
(He crushed the gamtae into a powder.)
(After picking up a fistful of tuna pollack roe mayo...)
- I see. Rice balls. - It's rolled up?
It's rolled up after filling it up?
- Like this? - I see.
(After the powdered gamtae is added generously,)
(the tuna pollack roe mayo rice ball comes to life.)
(He makes several of them for him to eat.)
He came up with a simple meal.
- But he knows how to eat. - Right.
That looks good. Gosh, that's nice.
(The well-cooked steamed eggs get taken out.)
(A savory flavor is added with a little bit of sesame oil.)
I expected him to have a poor meal.
Right. Seeing how he has steamer,
- Right. - he knows how to make good meals.
I enjoy cooking.
I'm not very good, but I enjoy cooking.
You like making things in general.
Right.
That's hot.
The reason for making these dishes?
Actually, it was for one dish.
He must've bought something.
(He takes out a mysterious bag out from the fridge?)
- What could it be? - What could it be? Chicken feet?
- Raw fish? - Chicken feet or cartilage?
(He takes out a mysterious bag out from the fridge?)
Chicken feet?
He must've bought something.
(Excited)
- What could it be? - What could it be? Chicken feet?
- Raw fish? - Chicken feet or cartilage?
(What could that be?)
Chicken feet?
- Cold chicken feet. - Cold chicken feet.
- Cold chicken feet? - With rice balls,
- That calls for soju. - you must have chicken feet.
I always go to Paju for that.
You drive for an hour to have that?
- Yes. - It must be his favorite.
- That's understandable. - A round trip of two hours.
(He's fine with going on a round trip of two hours for it.)
- But the chicken feet are huge. - They're really big.
- They're really big. - They're really big.
They must be that big to be enjoyed properly.
(Amazed)
This is insane.
(He coats his stomach with the soft steamed eggs.)
(Satisfied)
(This time, he goes for the gamtae rice ball.)
It's the whole set including the scorched rice.
- Steamed eggs as well. - Right.
(Satisfied)
- He's really enjoying it. - It was really good.
- He eats well. - Chicken feet...
will always be best buddies with rice balls.
(He doesn't hesitate to take a bite of the cold chicken feet.)
(Turning)
(He diligently debones it in his mouth.)
(Groaning)
It's so spicy!
- It's really spicy. - Right.
- It's really spicy. - I can't eat spicy things.
- I can't have more than three. - Come on.
- I'm serious. - It can't be that spicy.
- I can't eat spicy things. - I thought you would sleep...
after having a bit of salt and whisky for dinner.
- No way! - Come on.
- That feels like the last meal. - Is it tequila or what?
I thought that was all he would have.
(DAWN fixes up great meals for himself.)
His eyes look a lot bigger than in the morning.
It's spicy.
- Gosh. - They must be that spicy.
It's really spicy.
It's really spicy, but it's really good.
Gosh, it's so good.
Another day went by without any issues,
and I loved that.
This is my favorite phrase.
"No news is good news."
- As there was no news today, - Gosh.
I was able to do things I could do while taking a break.
I tell everyone to try living alone.
I tell this to anyone.
There's a reason for this. Actually, living alone is tough.
- You feel lonely, - Right. You feel lonely.
and there are many things you have to do.
But being on your own is the only way...
- to learn about yourself. - Right.
Right.
I always thought I was a perfect person.
But one day, I realized I was very lacking.
While being alone, you can experience the joy...
- of overcoming your lack. - Right.
Life felt so beautiful after thinking that way.
I wondered if this was...
the true joy of living life.
- That's wise. - I heard you fell asleep...
after saying that.
I was half-asleep.
"I wondered if this was..."
"Please save me!"
(Fully enjoying life)
- It must be really spicy. - Gosh.
- It must be really spicy. - It was really spicy.
(Lips swelling up)
(Drenched in sweat)
Haetnim.
Let's clean up and go for a walk.
(Life is Beautiful)
We should go for a walk.
(DAWN's Life is Beautiful)
Gosh, this is too spicy.
That was great.
(We enjoyed watching DAWN's life.)
- That was great. - That was great.
- After watching that, - Right.
it reminded me of when I first appeared on the show.
I ordered spicy jokbal and ate it.
It reminded me of those times.
He's forcing himself to find something in common.
The forced docking is insane.
He's forcing it.
He's forcing it when it doesn't even fit.
- There was nothing in common. - Isn't the spicy flavor...
the only thing that's similar?
That's not true.
- He's denying things now. - He's denying things now.
- He sounded firm. - Right.
- They're parallel to each other. - You tried to find any connection.
I'm not sure if I can say this,
but he feels like a male version of Kim Shin Young.
- Gosh. - She's docking as well.
- I don't think you can say that. - They're saying whatever they want.
Besides that we're both Kims,
- we don't have anything in common. - Is that so?
- Well, - Gosh.
he likes making things, just like I do.
He also spent a lot of time,
thinking about his future and how to live in joy.
- A male version of Kim Shin Young. - Of Kim Shin Young?
(He's a lot like me.)
- What did you think, Kian84? - I thought that he would be...
in a culture of enjoying things like parties.
- Right. - It was quite a twist.
- Right. - I go out often as well.
- You do? - Yes.
He was right about you, then.
- Then... - Gosh.
Then...
- You were right about him. - Right.
- You have great insight. - He has great insight.
- So one day... - It wasn't a whole week of him.
- Two days are spent like that. - He just gave me goosebumps.
He doesn't live like that 365 days a year.
- There was more to it. - Right.
Then, he's no longer the male version of Kim Shin Young.
- Right. - I also like going to clubs.
- What? - I saw him.
- I actually saw him. - In a club?
You saw me?
- Well, - You go clubbing?
I saw him going into a club from outside.
But he looked really excited.
(Flustered)
- I'm serious. - Wasn't it your first time?
I'm not lying about this at all.
I thought to myself, "Dae Ho was that bright?"
Really?
- What are you doing? - He went in like this.
Gosh!
- I'm serious. - That's so corny.
I'm not lying about this.
Who goes into a club like that?
(I won't do that again.)
I don't want to copy him without any meaning.
I want to learn more about him in a deeper way.
For the first time,
I thought that I wanted to copy him with meaning.
Before, I wanted to copy anyone without any meaning.
Gosh, the docking begins again.
- Hyun Moo! - I want to learn about him first.
- I won't copy him right away. - That's smart.
I want to copy him while creating content.
Isn't this the start of the Moo-DAWN Couple?
Moo-DAWN.
- The Moo-DAWN life. - Moo-DAWN!
- Moo-DAWN. - Moo-DAWN.
- Moo and DAWN. - Right. We'll collab as well.
- Another collaboration? - Of course.
(I Live Alone)
(The three men have gathered for a real run.)
(Kian84, MINHO, Na Ra)
(Today's course is a mountain path of around 13km.)
(Campsite, Turning Point 1, Turning Point 2)
(After passing through the slippery mud,)
(the endless staircase of the underworld appears.)
(Kian84 and MINHO look fine running the tough mountain path.)
(I want to walk.)
(No. Walking will make it tougher!)
(No. I want to walk!)
(Na Ra,)
(did you think about the Fun Run at that moment?)
(You did, didn't you?)
(I didn't think about the Fun Run.)
(Sulky)
(Crew-Chief84 pulls Na Ra, who is struggling.)
(I always think about this when I'm struggling toward the end!)
(I've gone through all of those struggles...)
(for this.)
(Kian84 was so impressive when he grabbed Na Ra's arm.)
(MINHO's character shines brightly just like his face.)
(Let's do a full sprint for the last 100m!)
(After pushing and pulling each other,)
(they managed to complete the 13km course.)
(Keep this in mind. I'm the chief.)
Of course.
(Crew chief)
(Training director)
(Cooking director)
(Shall we wash up now that we've set our roles?)
(I've seen it all!)
(Na Ra's...)
(MINHO's...)
(Twitching)
(Everything...)
(was seen.)
(Creeped out)
(This can be a reason to leave the crew.)
Are we going to eat?
- We should eat. - I'm so hungry.
To have some beer together,
- I prepared a snack. - What kind of snack?
Do you know cold pork slices?
Of course!
- I prepared cold pork slices. - It's the cooking director.
- I love cold pork slices. - It has begun.
Your favorite time has begun.
(Relieved)
As it might not be enough,
I prepared bibim ramyeon...
and whelks.
- They're great together. - Really?
I love having carbs.
Carbs are important.
- As it might not be enough, - Yes?
I have in mind the store that I spotted earlier.
(Amazed)
Then...
This isn't something that deserves a high-five.
I'll go to the store if we need more food.
- Let's go. - Right.
- Then, - I'll be back.
- should I be helping him? - Sure.
- Sounds great. - Okay.
How are we such a great team?
(Feeling proud)
They're so cute.
(Smirking)
You prepared all of this?
It isn't something incredible.
What's this?
- Dried pollack. - Dried pollack?
- I wanted to make it crispy. - Gosh, dried pollack is good.
I tried my best to grill them.
(He takes a bite right away.)
- It's so crispy. - Is it okay?
I'll come up with the sauce.
(It's so good.)
Great.
- Oyster sauce? - Gosh.
That was insane after being mixed with mayonnaise.
(Sprinkling)
These are garlic sesame seeds.
- Really? - Garlic sesame seeds!
- Do you know them? - I bought it at Don Quijote.
(Getting up)
(Do you know them?)
(They're from Don Quijote!)
- Gosh, I can finally speak. - Hold on.
- Hold on. - Sung Hwan!
Shin Young got up after two hours.
Shin Young!
(The three ran endlessly,)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(and her talking pace noticeably dropped.)
(Groaning)
(Frustrated)
(Just have rice or noodles at my place!)
(Smiling brightly)
They taste great when used in ramyeon!
I'm so glad.
(She perfectly recovers her pace thanks to the cooking director.)
This is a happy world.
Can I try some?
When I went on a diet,
- Yes? - I only had this with beer.
- Really? - Try some.
- It's good, isn't it? - What is this?
You can taste it...
- What is that? - Right from the start.
- I love this. - It's a new world.
It's really good when sprinkled on a poached egg.
This is amazing!
- You brought all of this? - Yes.
This is why an experienced camper feels different.
You have to get things prepared at home...
to feel comfortable at the campsite.
- Na Ra looked so impressive. - That's amazing.
To be honest, I was able to gain confidence...
after entering the tent.
I'm being honest.
- Oh, really? - Yes, a little.
- I see. - I gained confidence.
- What's that? I see. - I'll use it later for cold pork.
- You're here. - You're back already?
Yes.
I'll make soju bombs for both of you.
I'd love that.
It's easy for things to get dirty fast...
- What's that? - at campsites.
- Is that alcohol? - That's right.
This is so contrary.
You're using alcohol to wipe that,
but Kian84 is adding ice with his hand.
It doesn't matter.
- I'm adding alcohol here anyway. - I don't mind.
They're meeting in the middle.
He's too hygienic that people like me are criticized.
Because of people like me...
What's that? A knife?
You need to cut it with a beautiful knife...
to feel...
- Isn't that a Chinese cleaver? - It is.
- It is. - That's amazing.
Before we have our drinks, let me serve you...
(Cutting cold pork slices)
Since it was a meal on a hot day,
I put a lot of thought into it.
- Since it's too hot to grill meat. - That's right, Hyun Moo.
- For the first round, - Yes.
- I'll give you a piece each. - Goodness.
Then we should clink our glasses...
- After clinking our glasses, - and have a bite.
- we'll have a sip. - That's right.
Then we'll have a bite.
- Gosh. - Here. Great job.
- Great job. - Great job.
(Gulping down)
Kian84, here you go.
(Delivering the cold pork slice after sipping)
Gosh, it's good.
Hey, this is delicious.
- Gosh. - The cold pork slices...
- Hey, this is delicious. - must be delicious.
- That's better on a hot day. - Is it good?
I'm glad.
(Na Ra takes a bite after hearing their compliments.)
It's so good.
Gosh, it's so good.
I'll cut some more for you.
(Taking a big bite with green onion salad on top)
The green onion salad must be so good.
It was tender even though it was cold.
- Right? - Yes.
I'm glad you like it.
It's worth all the effort I put into making it yesterday.
Have a piece with the skin.
The skin on the five-layer pork belly is chewy.
(MINHO feeds the cooking director who worked hard.)
Thank you.
I should give you more delicious parts.
(They can't stop eating it.)
I'm glad you like it.
It's so good.
Seriously.
(He keeps feeding them meat with pleasure.)
Na Ra, you should eat some.
- You should eat too. - Yes, I will.
We were talking earlier, and Na Ra...
I noticed this since the retreat.
I actually thought...
you'd be a bit cold.
When I saw you in "Weak Hero Class 2,"
- I thought you were a psychopath. - So...
So the drama...
- I thought you were a psychopath. - So the drama...
- Those who watched it get it. - Really?
- You can't help but think that way. - That's right.
I thought you'd be merciless.
- You seemed so cold. - Right. So,
I also thought he'd be cold in real life too.
(Na Ra always took care of others.)
He's really delicate and thoughtful.
- Right? - And he speaks sweetly.
I felt like I became a child after a long while...
when I was talking with you.
(Moved)
Gosh, this is nice.
This is really nice.
Why would you drink by yourself?
- What? Here. - Cheers.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Isn't it about time we decide our crew's name?
Yes, let's make one.
Do you have a crew of your own?
I don't have a running crew.
It's my first running crew.
- Really? - I don't have one.
How shall we name it?
(How shall we name our crew?)
I don't want it to be cringey.
- Me neither. - Right.
What really matters is what's essential.
(What should we call ourselves?)
- Then... - People of the Street.
People of the Street?
It's the most cringey.
People of the Street is the worst.
Street Crew.
- Street Crew. - Yes.
- Street Crew? - It sounds like a hip-hop...
(Thinking)
There's nothing like Moo Do Ra Ji.
Then let's use the latest technology.
(He even uses an AI as they're not impressed.)
Three Steps.
- Use the paid version. - Maybe because I was a Marine.
Three Steps Crew.
- But more could join our crew. - That's the problem.
Then it'll be Four Steps or Five steps.
- The name will keep changing. - That's right.
How about this? Since we all live alone...
(Blank Crew)
Not bad.
How about this? Since we all live alone,
how about Alone Crew?
- Alone Crew? Not bad. - People who live alone can join.
- That sounds good. - Alone Crew?
- Alone Crew? - Let's call ourselves Alone Crew.
Sounds good.
- Alone Crew. - Alone Crew.
(That sounds good.)
- Let's drink to that. - Alone Crew!
- Alone Crew! - Alone Crew!
(They unanimously decide to call themselves Alone Crew.)
- Alone Crew. - I really like the name.
- It sounds good, right? - Yes.
(Even the last Fun Run member is swaying?)
The name is nice.
- It's nice, right? - The name is nice.
Those who want to join must live alone.
- Those who like running. - Those who like running.
I think that those who want to join our crew...
could have a hard time to express their will to join.
So...
(Because of Hyun Moo,)
(you can't say it easily, right, Ji Hyeon?)
Those who want to join my crew, call me privately.
Alone Crew.
I love the name.
Why are you only staring at Ji Hyeon?
- He takes turns. One, two. - To see if he joins that crew.
Three.
(They've decided on their crew name.)
Are we having bibim ramyeon right away?
- I'll make it. - They should.
(He starts making bibim ramyeon that MINHO brought.)
(The cooking director boils noodles skillfully.)
Thank you for cooking everything.
Oh, not at all.
You're indeed our cooking director.
Since we ran a lot, we should restore nutrients.
(Adding the whelks that MINHO brought)
This is nice.
(Mix it thoroughly.)
(Bibim ramyeon with whelk is ready.)
It'll be tasty with a bit of pepper.
That's right, pepper.
- I wanted to mention that too. - Right?
I thought something was missing. It was pepper.
- And have it with whelk. - That's right.
- With bibim ramyeon. - It won't smell like flour.
It'll be even more delicious with a bit of jjolmyeon.
Shin Young doesn't stop talking now that it's about food.
She's going wild.
- I'm MINHO when it comes to food. - You're an expert.
Of course. I never get tired.
(They begin Round 2 in earnest.)
- Will it get soggy? - What? No.
- All right. You have it first. - Have it first.
- Thank you, Na Ra. - Sure.
I won't refuse and eat it first.
It looks really good.
(The chief of Alone Crew tries it first.)
- It's impossible to taste bad. - It must be really good.
Of course it's good.
(MINHO takes a big bite too.)
Have it with whelk.
(Yes, this is it.)
Thank you for the food.
(The cooking director takes a big bite as well.)
(It's so good!)
(Putting)
Kian84, stop.
Have it with that.
(Putting it into his mouth)
They enjoyed it so much.
- It was really good, though. - Nothing can beat bibim ramyeon.
- I'm happy. - Yes.
Seriously.
- He eats so well. - Because we ran all day,
- I could keep eating. - That's right.
You must be mistaken. It's delicious even if you don't run.
It's delicious even if you eat it after lying down.
- It's good if you eat lying down. - Of course.
(While they're enjoying their meal,)
(the sun slowly sets.)
I don't know why I keep mentioning Hyun Moo.
I really wished Hyun Moo would run with me for real.
- Really? - He was serious about it?
I wanted to run the 10km race with him.
He said he'd never do it.
But he came up with Fun Run.
That's why...
- That means you were upset. - Right.
If Hyun Moo hears this,
he could...
- He won't. He would never. - run with you.
- He'd never run. - I mentioned it many times.
He's not going to do it.
All he does is this instead of running.
(Spot-on)
- That uses up so much energy. - This?
- I know. - It could kill you.
I hope you don't do weird things.
You call that a weird thing?
I want you to run with me properly.
This crew is quite fascinating.
It's relaxing and friendly.
- I know. - And they gossip too.
- It's about everyday life. - Wait.
It's unusual.
- We can't do without Hyun Moo. - Yes, you're right.
It's like we can't do without you...
when we run.
- Gosh, listen to what he says. - That's right.
- Seriously. - I mean that much?
Yes, you mean that much.
- Let's run again next time. - You mean that much.
(I'd love that.)
Was it not enough?
Shall we have this next?
- Yes, let's have that. - Yes, it's simple.
Just try tasting it.
- Do you need water? - Yes.
- Should I leave it? - No.
- I need it. - You do?
- Should I leave it? - No. I need it.
This... Wait. You need that too?
- I need that. - Really?
- I'm really curious, though. - Yes?
I don't know what you're going to add to that.
What is he going to make? Gosh.
The ingredients for my dish came from the site.
You shouldn't ask that.
Is that so? Okay.
You should just have those for now.
(Anxious)
Let's have the food the chief makes.
- Let's trust him. - Yes, let's trust him.
Let's wait and see.
(It'll be delicious.)
This is the dish I prepared.
If I were to describe it with my philosophy...
It's fine dump.
- Wait. Fine dump? - Gosh.
- What kind of fine dining is that? - I hate it.
- I won't hate it. - I hate the name itself.
- That's right. Dump is... - Fine dump?
- It sounds cool with "fine." - Fine dump.
I hate that it's dump.
You could've called it something else.
"Fine dining" and "find dump..."
are not that different.
- Gosh. - There's only a slight difference.
No, I hate that it's dump.
- But the way it looks... - I wonder how it tastes.
deserves its name.
You'll know if you watch it until the end.
- I'm curious. - Just watch until the end.
It's fine dump.
I added all the leftovers in the ramyeon pot.
That way, we can finish...
all the food we brought that day.
That was my philosophy. "Let's add all the leftovers."
(Fine dump dining dreams of a world with no leftover food.)
(He begins getting rid of all the leftovers.)
Let's add this.
You added instant rice without heating it, right?
- No, I didn't. - That way, the grains are firm.
- Is it like risotto? - That's right.
So far, it's ramyeon and rice.
Oh, dear...
- What is it? - Nothing.
(Grabbing)
It's not fine dump dining yet.
Oh, here it is.
(Adding the leftover pork slices)
That's how they fed dogs...
- in the countryside in the past. - That's right!
(That's how they fed dogs in the countryside in the past.)
- They had leftover jjigae too. - Dogs like them...
live healthy and long.
They lived long. You're right.
- They took so many nutrients. - That's right.
They didn't even need vaccinations.
You guys shouldn't get vaccinations either.
- We were... - What do you mean?
vaccinated by Kian84.
- Vaccinated by Kian84? - It's perfect.
- Great. - You got the primary vaccination.
You won't catch a cold in winter.
- Of course not. - Yes.
Does that mean Kian84 is a germ?
Or virus.
- Your immunity will strengthen. - Ji Hyeon.
- Hold on, I've heard enough. - That's not what I meant.
- Virus! - Ji Hyeon!
- You're not wary of me at all! - Ji Hyeon.
- I mean... - Well done.
- He wasn't like this before. - Wait, this is...
- He's the best. - I mean, the logic is...
Ji Hyeon is... Gosh.
(He was just curious about the virus for the vaccination.)
(Dropping)
(Smiling)
- Why would you watch me? - No.
- I won't watch. - I just...
- I was just thinking. - It's not that bad.
(While MINHO is thinking...)
What? There's so much left.
(He adds kimchi calmly.)
- That's... - That's not a bad combination.
It's not bad.
(Rustling)
- Do you need garlic? - Oh, we had garlic too.
- There's Cheongyang chili too. - Good.
- That'd be really nice. - Oh, garlic?
It's a waste if we throw it.
Right. It's a waste.
He has a different perspective.
We have to throw it...
if we don't use it, so we must use it.
That's why the seasoning...
changes depending on how much food is left.
I see.
He hates wasting food.
- That's a good attitude. - Of course.
I gave a lot of thought into our crew's course.
I thought, "Should I try a city run that I haven't tried?"
That sounds fun too.
But there's this thing called shamanism running.
It's going to scary places where ghosts appear.
You have to run past a haunted house.
- It's a dawn run. - It's running in the mountains...
- past a haunted house. - It's so scary.
A graveyard run.
You get a crazy dopamine rush.
- You'll run like crazy. - And...
Our pace will go up.
Can't we do that first in summer?
Since it's summer now.
- I think... - I love them both.
- You'll run like crazy. - Our pace will go up.
- Actually, - Sounds interesting.
- a haunted house run is... - A haunted house run?
It's a little tough.
It's a big tough in a different way because of fear.
- You need to bet your life. - I...
don't know if I can say this,
but as the crew's training director,
- let me say something. - Sure.
I was a Marine who caught ghosts.
- It's so cool that he was a Marine. - Let's see if he doesn't scream.
- Gosh. - How charismatic.
(Dignified)
- He's so cool. - Wait.
(Marine MINHO's fighting spirit is surging at the mention of a ghost.)
(Happy)
(You were a Marine?)
I was a Marine who caught ghosts.
Auxiliary police officer Kian84.
You'd die too if a ghost appears, you punk.
That's what I wanted to say.
- Ghosts are really scary. - I have no problem.
- Seriously, I... - Ghosts are so scary.
I can take care of it.
- Really? - Yes.
I can see how MINHO would be 30 to 40 years later.
Seriously.
Me too.
- "Which batch were you in?" - "Which batch were you in?"
"You're so young, yet you can't run. Run!"
I'm so glad I wasn't born as his son or grandson.
I'd have been in trouble every holiday.
Let me add one more thing.
Not just anyone can take a photo in front of the First Division.
Oh, my gosh!
- Having that honor at that age... - A Marine...
- I got to because I won an award. - Really?
He's different.
I got a commendation from the division commander.
(The privilege of an award winner)
- It's scary. - I'm proud of him, though.
He's so cool.
I feel so proud.
(Fluttering)
That's right.
(Once a Marine, always a Marine.)
It smells delicious, though.
(While they were talking, the smell of ramyeon and rice spreads.)
It looks delicious.
- Gosh, the smell... - It looks delicious.
- Gosh. - The color doesn't look bad.
It smells amazing.
Nothing can beat this.
(Salivating)
Goodness.
It's totally Kian84's style.
Because it has garlic...
and kimchi...
It's refreshing.
As soon as he placed the pot,
I was surprised.
The visuals and the smell were crazy good.
"What is this?"
(He was excited at the unfamiliar smell.)
I was looking forward to it.
Yes, I wonder how it tastes.
- I think we'll finish it. - Yes.
- Try it. - Yes.
- Thank you for cooking. - Thank you for cooking.
Sorry. Let me take a photo.
Hurry up and take one.
(Halting)
Yes, let's take a photo.
(Click)
- Yes, let's take a photo. - You're the first ones...
to take a photo of my food.
(Emotional)
I'll take a photo of you two. Get closer.
You're the first ones to take a photo of my food.
Others were disgusted by his food.
Why are you crying?
It looks great too.
It looks delicious. What's wrong?
I can't believe you took a photo of it.
Thank you.
- Kian84 was really moved. - I know.
My food has always been looked down on.
(Moved)
- Thank you for this. - Help yourself.
It was...
I was grateful.
- He's broken. - He's broken.
There was no one...
who took a photo of my food.
I almost cried then.
You were really emotional.
I guess I've felt upset all along.
They'd be like, "Why do you eat like such food?"
I guess it was bottled up without me knowing.
You must've been upset.
(The photo Na Ra took, the photo MINHO took)
I don't know why they took a photo of that.
Honestly, I don't like it when people take a photo of food.
I'd be like, "You'll eat them up anyway. Why bother taking a photo?"
But they took a photo of it as though a chef made it.
I was grateful for that.
They're such good friends.
Thank you.
(Touched)
I had too much noodles earlier,
- so I should have rice now. - I know.
(They finally try it after taking photos.)
- After tasting it... - I bet it's good.
(Expectant)
- Are you satisfied with it? - Is it okay?
Isn't it a bit bland?
It's okay. It's not bad.
It must be good.
(Na Ra takes a bite too.)
(Exclaiming)
- You guys... - It's delicious.
- It's delicious. - Seriously...
Eat your fill, guys.
What's the closest food you can describe it to?
- Budae jjigae? - Budae jjigae?
At first, it tasted like omori kimchi jjigae.
- Oh, omori kimchi jjigae? - That's right.
- Was the kimchi aged? - Aged kimchi.
- Like aged kimchi jjigae. - I'm even more grateful...
that you called it omori.
(Moved)
(Slurping)
(MINHO inhales everything.)
It was really good.
- It was so good... - I know.
- You're eating from the bowl. - that I'm salivating even now.
- Really? - Yes.
(Gulping)
(Na Ra enjoys the ramyeon and rice too.)
I wanted to try the food that Kian84 cooked.
I realized it today...
that he's confident in dishes like that.
Also,
I found its characteristic.
He doesn't add the ingredients that could be reused.
But he adds the ones that we would throw.
You're spot on.
- Gosh. - You're spot on.
You're like a mind reader.
- You know exactly what he means. - I mean...
You're precisely right.
He adds ingredients that'd be thrown out that day.
- The ones you won't use. - You're right.
- You can have the rest next time. - That's right.
He only adds the ones that'd go bad.
It's not that I want to have food that's spoiled.
Of course not.
Gosh, Kian84.
- It's successful. - It's good. I'm glad.
It's good.
What do you make often these days?
I make steamed fish intestine.
- What? Steamed fish intestine? - Fish intestine and roe?
(He can't believe what he heard.)
I mix fish intestine...
and a bit of meat.
That's the level I'm at.
(He's slowly developing his cooking skill.)
I didn't mention it because I was embarrassed.
- Can I speak my mind honestly? - What is it?
I want to try steamed fish intestine with meat.
- Right. - Is that so?
- I thought so too. - After having that,
I wanted to try the other dish.
(Is that so?)
- I'll make it for you next time. - All right.
- Steamed fish intestine with meat. - I'll make it for you.
I'm suddenly excited for it.
- If it's made with pork belly... - I'll make it for you.
(Exhilarated)
- If it's made with pork belly... - Right.
- With pork belly. - I'll make it after our next run.
Pork belly and fish intestine.
You're not saying that to console me, are you?
- No. - No, it's because this was good.
- Because it was good? - Yes.
Even if it's just ramyeon and rice,
I keep going back for it because it's good.
Gosh, thank you.
The highlight of the day.
- Everything was successful today. - Yes.
For real.
This is nice.
(Getting up)
It's nothing amazing.
- You can play the guitar? - For real?
- What is it? - I'm not so good at it.
But I brought it so we could sing together.
That's crazy.
- You prepared so much. - You prepared a lot.
Actually, I prepared for college entrance...
to major in applied music.
I always bring a guitar or a keyboard...
when I go camping in summer.
- That's so romantic. - Romantic.
Don't expect too much.
I just enjoy playing it.
We saw how good you are at the retreat.
You'll be surprised when you see him play.
- Really? - Yes.
Gosh, he's really good.
(Expectant)
(Starting sweetly)
He's good at singing too.
(Happy)
I think he fell in love with Na Ra.
His eyes have gone big.
It looks like he fell in love at first sight. Wait.
You should propose to him right after.
(Laughing)
(On a difficult day)
(If you leave also)
(Where can I go when I need someone to lean on?)
It's nice to hear that again.
- It's crazy romantic. - Actually...
- What is this, Na Ra? - I'm getting sentimental.
When I go camping,
I enjoy being sentimental and romantic.
(A gift from Na Ra, a romance lover)
You're so talented.
What's with the look in his eyes?
His eyes are...
- What is this? - What's wrong with him?
- Wait. - What's wrong with your eyes?
- You look pervy. - What was that?
It's like you're saying, "You're mine."
That's it, isn't it? It's so gross.
(Familiar sights hidden in the monotony)
Gosh, this is...
(Laughing)
(Why? What is this song?)
(It's Kian84's first solo song, "Dandelion.")
So this is "Dandelion."
It's Kian84's song. You prepared a lot.
(Shy)
("Dandelion" found its spring day after 2 years.)
Gosh, this is embarrassing.
(A sweet voice...)
(that melts your heart)
It was a nice song.
It was a masterpiece.
- The unknown flowers - The unknown flowers
(They take root)
(Singing)
It's embarrassing.
- All right. - It's embarrassing.
It was moving because he prepared...
- to sing that for me. - It's moving.
He's really good.
(Na Ra is good.)
- You set the tempo - You set the tempo
What's wrong with him?
Because he sang my song,
I couldn't help but make that face.
(It's MINHO's solo song, "TEMPO.")
It's a dance song, but he changed it into an acoustic version.
- Really? - Yes.
Five, six, seven.
(Let's sing together.)
(Super mellow)
(A thoughtfully customized playlist)
- It's a song that goes like this. - It's a song like this.
He's so thoughtful.
(He's amazing.)
(Na Ra continues to sing a medley of romantic songs.)
What?
(Let's not cry when we break up)
It's Ji Hyeon's song.
- This is fun. - It's my song.
(Ji Hyeon's "Mu" brings out his powerful vocals.)
(Life is nothing that complicated)
(It's just a dream)
(Proper Run Crew's night grows deeper with romance.)
I love it!
(I love it.)
- He became a fan. - I love it.
I think he'll join Proper Run Crew.
- Ji Hyeon! - He's joining us.
- Ji Hyeon! - I think he'll join them.
Let's go!
- Shall we run together? - Let's go, Ji Hyeon!
(Shall I run with Alone Crew?)
- Let's go! - Wait a minute.
You're blinded.
What?
Gosh.
- Are you joining Proper Run Crew? - Hyun Moo is feeling anxious!
Proper Run Crew!
- He has no one now. - There really is no one now.
You were the only one for me
I love it.
I like Ji Hyeon's version better.
(Flirting with him when he has the chance)
(The night deepens with romance.)
- That's it. - These days,
I'm paying a lot of attention...
to spending a meaningful day.
I ran really hard and felt my limits,
so I ran out of energy.
But it helped me have productive thoughts...
like, "How can I improve my skills?"
(Endless effort to grow)
It was a productive day.
That's so healthy.
As for Fun Run, it was about having a fun day.
- I love you, Hyun Moo. - The enemy was within.
As for Proper Run Crew,
I wanted to run with them again.
I think Kian84 is a special leader.
He leads us from the front.
In case we get tired,
he'd push us from behind.
I learned a lot from him today.
I don't force others.
If we get to run together again...
I want to keep running with them.
(Alone Crew kept running together since that day.)
(A strong bond formed through running)
We're maintaining our crew.
I heard Fun Run Crew isn't running anymore.
- Based on the comments... - Who said we stopped running?
- We will run too. - Yes, we will.
- You will, right? - Yes.
(Good luck.)
It's not a compliment about me,
but in a modern world,
leaders like me are a better fit.
That's a compliment about you.
"You're a good runner,"
"so you should be the training director."
"You play the guitar well,"
"so you should be our entertainment director."
Allowing them to grow...
is what makes me a true leader.
A person like me...
is a true leader.
I'm a true Maitreya.
Today is your last day, right?
- He even mentioned Maitreya? - Why would he mention that?
I mean, Maitreya?
You're amazing.
(Alone Crew, forever)
I didn't know this was possible.
I can't believe Fun Run Crew...
took a talented man like him.
You're attacking us again?
I mean, you mentioned us...
- more than 150 times! - Seriously!
- There's no end to it. - I mean...
When I was about to forget...
We gathered to gossip about Fun Run Crew.
It's a crew that's already dead.
- Why do you keep mentioning it? - I know.
I wasn't even breathing, and you kept shooting at me.
To maintain our crew,
- I needed a reason. - Change your crew's name.
- What Alone Crew? - He kept shooting at me.
Why do I keep attacking Fun Run Crew?
I know. Why do you keep mentioning them?
- I guess it was bottled up. - You were.
They were such an eyesore.
He always ends up mentioning Fun Run Crew.
I keep attacking them. I feel bad.
(Next story)
(Gosh, it looks amazing.)
I feel like I'm watching a show.
Goodness, this is...
(To celebrate Chobok,)
(I invited my friends.)
(I'll let you enjoy Chobok to the fullest.)
(They know each other so well.)
(Pepper Sister, Shin Young)
(Rainbow Club's representative chunk)
(Ham Brother, Seon Min)
(Min, Hwan, and Young)
Look at Young.
(Welcome to Hwan's house.)
(You're hungry because you worked, right?)
(I'm really hungry.)
(You guys should rest.)
Goodness, this is crazy.
(I'll make it delicious.)
(It's so spicy.)
(Coughing)
(Are you okay?)
(Save me!)
(The conflict intensifies as her coughing gets worse.)
(You'll be doomed if you open a restaurant.)
(What is this? Don't do it.)
(Upset)
(Leave.)
(You want us to leave?)
(It was really hard.)
(I regret it even to this day.)
(It Was Chobok)
(It's been a while.)
(This is Shanghai.)
(A place filled with memories from Ji Hyeon's childhood)
(My old neighborhood I came back to after a long time)
(This street looks the same.)
(Hey, that's my school!)
(He enters his old school excitedly.)
(I can't believe I'm back here.)
(Smiling bashfully)
(Jumping like the little child he was 20 years ago)
(He trudges on, leaving behind an armful of memories.)
What is this?
(What is everyone doing out here?)
(Is this where people get married?)
(It's where they have blind dates.)
(I can meet someone...)
(if I want to?)
(Which year were you born?)
(Is this what you're looking for?)
(A sudden chance to get married?)
(- Where are you from? - From Korea.)
(Suddenly singing "Arirang")
(A surprise serenade he didn't even request?)
(Shanghai Once Again)